Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, History, 1963-2018 UPG.RG.00
ULS Greensburg
- Policy Statements, 1995-2017; VIII.
  University of Pittsburgh: Affirmative Action Policies: Notice to Students with Disabilities; Sexual Harassment, Anti-Harassment Policy, Nondiscrimination Policy Statement [Sept. 2006] Alcohol Policy [changes 2010] Alcohol Policy [News Article, "The History and Future of Pitt-Greensburg's Alcohol Policy", The Insider n.s. v.10 #3, Mar. 2019, p.1-2]. Anti-Harassment Policy Statement (Sept. 2001) Assistance for Victims of Sexual Assault [1996] Drug-Free Workplace, Drug-Free Schools Policy (Sept. 1993, Sept. 1994) Guidelines for Ethical Practices in Research (May 1997) Extreme Weather Conditions, Policy on. 1995. Fireside Lounge Policy. 12/04/06 Harassment and Nondiscrimination Policies. November 2004. Involuntary Military Service Commitment, Procedures Upon. 2003. Nondiscrimination Policy Statement (Sept. 2001) Political Activity Locations & Regulations [Memo Rick A. Fogle 9/19/2016]. Raising Funds, New Policy Raises Requirements for [2007] Script Pitt Logo, Authorized. [JBK memo 5/19/16] Sexual Harassment Complaints. Prepared by the Sexual Harassment Task Force 1997. Reprinted 1999 Sexual Harassment Complaints. Prepared by the Sexual Harassment Task Force 1. Reprinted in 2004. Sexual Harassment Policy (Sept. 2001) Sexual Violence, Reporting Incidents of [Memo. dtd 2/20/15 SPS to University Community: Faculty, Staff, and Students. Sidewalk Chalking (2008) Smokeless Tobacco Policy 1995 Smoking Ban Policy [entranceways Powers Hall, Chambers Hall, and Smith Hall] 2007 Smoking Policy [UPG Campus Revised Policy effective beginning fall 2012 Term] Smoking Policy [Tobacco and Vapor Products] [Clarification of policy. 2/10/15] Social Media Protocol [UPG Campus Social Media Protocol] [2017] Student Code of Conduct and Judicial Procedures (effective Sept. 1990) Title IX: Reporting Proceedures and Resources [A Guide for Faculty and Staff Who Learn of Alleged Sexual Misconduct or Violence Involving a Student]. [201?] Usage of University Vans Use and Management of Social Security Numbers and University Primary ID ("UPI") Numbers 2005. Use of University Name, Logo and Service Marks, Use of [JBK memo 4/26/16] Weather Conditions, Extreme (undtd) Wireless PittNet Access and Use, Pitt-Greensburg Acceptable, 2016. [Version published August 15, 2014, Revised January 5, 2016.] The Pitt Promise: A Commitment to Civility. Poster, Flyers, and Sidewalk Chalk Policy. Updated 10/3/19.
  [Note: For text of policy statements, see RG38 Sudent Affairs, Ser.: Student Handbook.]
  See also RG02.4.1 Special Assistant to the President for Minority and Diversity Affairs. Ser.: Memoranda.
  - Policy Statements, 1995-2017 (File-cabinet 1, Drawer 2, Box 7)
- Proclamation, September 25, 2001; IX.
  House of Representatives, Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. [Cites the Westmoreland County Historical Society and the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg for initiating an annual Arthur St. Clair Lectureship in October; cites the Westmoreland County Historical Society for establishing the Arthur St. Clair Preservation Awards each October; cites the Westmoreland County Archaeological Society participation in the October "National Archaeology Month"; proclaims October 2001 to be commemorated as "Westmoreland Heritage Month".]
  [Housed in Map Case. See q RG00 History. Proclamation.]
  See also: RG02.4 Ser.: Publications. We Made No Small Plans: A Memoir by Dr. Frank A. Cassell. 2007.
  - Proclamation, September 25, 2001 (Map-case 1)